
export const Questions = [{

    prompt: "Who is the CEO of JurisTech?",
    optionA: "Kiarash",
    optionB: "John",
    optionC:"Hosein",
    optionD:"See Wai Hun",
    answer:"optionD",
},{
    prompt: "Which of this isn't JurisTech Solutions?",
    optionA: "Juris Sepctrum",
    optionB: "Juris Collect",
    optionC:"Juris Example",
    optionD:"Juris Anny",
    answer:"optionC",

},{
    prompt: "Who are the founders of JurisTech?",
    optionA: "John Lim & See Wai Hun",
    optionB: "Mr A & Mr.B",
    optionC:"Mr c & Mr.D",
    optionD:"Mrs E and Mr F",
    answer:"optionA",

},{
    prompt: "Which of this is not a programming language?",
    optionA: "Python",
    optionB: "JavaScript",
    optionC:"E=Mc2",
    optionD:"Java",
    answer:"optionC",

},{
    prompt: "What is the businees nature of JurisTech?",
    optionA: "Plantation",
    optionB: "Financial Technology Company",
    optionC:"Coffee shop",
    optionD:"Accounting ",
    answer:"optionB",

},{
    prompt: "Which one of this is the Subsidary of JurisTech?",
    optionA: "iMoney.my",
    optionB: "iPhone.my",
    optionC:"Johnmccafey.my",
    optionD:"RocknRoll",
    answer:"optionA",

},{
    prompt: "How much did CTOS acquire from JurisTech",
    optionA: "46%",
    optionB: "33%",
    optionC:"49%",
    optionD:"51%",
    answer:"optionC",

},{
    prompt: "Where does the HQ of JurisTech Located?",
    optionA: "K.L",
    optionB: "Johor",
    optionC:"Penang",
    optionD:"Ipoh",
    answer:"optionA",

},{
    prompt: "What are the core values GECO practices?",
    optionA: "Growing Heroes",
    optionB: "Huge like Sea",
    optionC:"Expanded Universe",
    optionD:"Core of Sun",
    answer:"optionA",

},{
    prompt: "Who is your latest employee?",
    optionA: "V.S.Naaviinesh",
    optionB: "Mr.X",
    optionC:"Mr.Y",
    optionD:"Mr.Z",
    answer:"optionA",

}]